RG 005:034, Office of the Governor: John Dempsey (1961-1971)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 11. Speeches with related materials, 1961-1970
  - Main Files, 1961-1970
    - Associated Press, Managing Editors, Hartford Hilton, 1969 (Box A-415)
    - Associated Press, Annual Meeting, Conn. Circuit, 1961 (Box A-415)
    - Asylum Hill Congregational Church, Hartford, 1965 (Box A-415)
    - Conn. Automotive Trades Association, 1961 (Box A-415)
    - Baldwin-Gegenheimer Corporation Opening Ceremonies, 1966 (Box A-415)
    - Baltimore Business Forms, Inc., 1966 (Box A-415)
    - Bankers Association, Conn., 1966 (Box A-415)
    - Baptist Missionary Convention, Connecticut - Hopewell Baptist Church, Hartford, 1965 (Box A-415)
    - Barbers, Conn. State 63rd Annual Convention, Hartford, 1964 (Box A-415)
    - Bartlett Arboretum Dedication, Stamford, 1966 (Box A-415)
    - Bear Path Elementary School Dedication Hamden, 1962 (Box A-415)
    - Bennington County Democratic Committee, Bennington, Vermont, 1967 (Box A-415)
    - Benrus Company Plant, Ridgefield, Conn., 1964 August 4 (Box A-415)
    - Benton Dinner, 1968 February 1 (Box A-415)
    - Berlin-Route 72, Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 1962 November 1 (Box A-415)
    - Lenten Service, Bethany Lutheran Church, Cromwell, 1969 March 12 (Box A-415)
    - Bethel AME Church, Hartford, 1963 (Box A-415)
    - Bethel AME Church 45th Anniversary Celebration, 1962 (Box A-415)
    - Beth-El Religious School, Beth-El Synagogue, Waterbury, 1962 (Box A-415)
    - Birdie Missile Site Dedication, Cromwell, 1962 (Box A-415)
    - Dr. Bloomberg Retirement Dinner, Hartford, 1969 (Box A-415)
    - Bloomfield Town Hall Dedication Ceremonies, 1962 (Box A-415)
    - B"nai B"rith Antidefamation League 10th Anniversary Dinner, 1961 (Box A-415)
    - B"nai B"rith Conn. Valley Council Kutsher's Country Club, 1964 April 25 (Box A-415)
    - Statement by Gov. Dempsey on Bombing Halt in Vietnam, 1968 (Box A-415)
    - Boys Club Association Bristol Forestville Boys Club, 1966 (Box A-415)
    - Boys and Girls State, University of Connecticut, 1965 (Box A-415)
    - Boys and Girls State, University of Connecticut, 1964 (Box A-415)
    - Kickoff Dinner, Boy Scouts Expansion Program, Hartford, 1967 November 7 (Box A-415)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Region 1, Massachusetts, 1967 October 2 (Box A-415)
    - Boy Scouts - Annual Scouters Banquet, 1965 (Box A-415)
    - Bradley Field - Dedication of Air Cargo Terminal, 1962 (Box A-415)
    - Bridgeport Ground Breaking Route 25, 1966 (Box A-415)
    - Bridgeport, Chamber of Commerce, 1961 (Box A-415)
    - Bridgeport, Engineering Institute Commencement Address, 1961 (Box A-415)
    - Bridgeport Traffic Association, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Bristol Chamber of Commerce Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Broadcast House WTIC (Box A-416)
    - Brotherhood in Action Program, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Brotherhood Banquet National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1969 (Box A-416)
    - Brotherhood Banquet National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Brotherhood Homes Dedication, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Bullard-Havens Vocational Technical School, Bridgeport, Commencement, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Catholic Charities Annual Dinner Meeting of Advisory Board, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Catholic Club of Norwalk Lincoln Day Banquet, Darien, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Catholic Guild for the Blind, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Catholic Nurses, Diocesan Councils of, 1963 (Box A-416)
    - Catholic Youth Organization, Northwest Catholic High School, 1964 (Box A-416)
    - Central Connecticut State College, 1968 (Box A-416)
    - Central Connecticut State College, Conferring of Honorary Membership in Kappa Delta Pi, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Central Connecticut State College 112th Annual Alumni Day Luncheon, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Chemical Industry Day, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Speech Channel 3 Governor's Committee on Hall of the House, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - 20th Anniversary - Channel 8 Taped Message, 1968 (Box A-416)
    - Channel 3, Statement before Com. on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Chicago- Detroit Trip, 1962 May (Box A-416)
    - Child Welfare League of America, New England Regional Conference, 1964 (Box A-416)
    - Christmas Message Taped Bill Potter, Jim Riegert (Box A-416)
    - Governors Conference on Children and Youth, Western Conn. State College, Danbury, 1968 (Box A-416)
    - Council on Children and Youth Services, 1969 (Box A-416)
    - Choice Vend Plant Dedication, 1963 (Box A-416)
    - Christian J. Orlean - Governor's Comments, 1966 May 12 (Box A-416)
    - Christmas Greetings to Conn. Servicemen, Taped by WTIC, 1969 (Box A-416)
    - Citizenship - New Britain Council on Annual Citizenship Day, New Britain, 1964 (Box A-416)
    - Civil Defense Conference for Women, 1964 (Box A-416)
    - Civil Defense Meeting, State Capitol, Hartford, 1963 January (Box A-416)
    - Speech - Civil Defense Conference, State Capitol, Hartford, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Speech - Civil Defense, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Civil Engineers, Conn. Society, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Civil Rights Rally, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Civil Rights Commission 20th Anniversary Banquet, Wallingford, 1963 (Box A-416)
    - Civitan Club Luncheon, Bridgeport, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Dedication - New Clairol Plant, Stamford, 1968 (Box A-416)
    - Clean Air Task Force, State Capitol, 1968 (Box A-416)
    - Clean Water Task Force Bill, Signing of, 1967 May 1 (Box A-416)
    - Clean Water Task Force Meeting, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Clean Water Task Force Organizational Meeting, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Coast Guard Academy (New London Day), 1964 (Box A-416)
    - USS Coates - Decommissioning Ceremonies, New Haven, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Colchester Democratic Rally, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - CBS Laboratories Dedication Exercises, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Commencement Remarks, 1968 June (Box A-416)
    - Columbus Day Celebration, Hamden, 1962 October 12 (Box A-416)
    - Community Chest-Red Cross Campaign, Greater Hartford, 1964 (Box A-416)
    - Community Conference on Federal Aid to Cities and Towns, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Dedication - Community Services Building, New Haven, 1967 (Box A-416)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Council, State Capitol, 1968 (Box A-416)
    - Conference on Educational Involvement in Teen-age Alcohol Use, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Conference on Research and Economic Growth, Conn. Research Commission, Westport, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Agricultural Experiment Station, Hamden, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Association for Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Association of Housing and Redevelopment Authorities, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - CR & L Bus Company Strike Meeting, 1967 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Association of Real Estate Boards, Hartford Hilton, 1970 October 8 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Association of Real Estate Boards, 1968 (Box A-416)
    - Real Estate Board Association, 1967 (Box A-416)
    - State Bar Association, 1967 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Association of Real Estate Boards, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Real Estate Boards Annual Convention, Hartford, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Real Estate Boards, Conn. Association of, 1964 (Box A-416)
    - Real Estate Boards, Conn. Association of, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Real Estate, Conn. Association of, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Real Estate Board of New Haven, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Bar Association Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Bar Association 9th Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Bar Association Annual Dinner, 1964 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Bar Association, 1963 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Broadcasters Association Distinguished Service Award Luncheon, 1965 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Building Congress Exposition and Symposium, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Building Congress, 1962 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Child Welfare Association Legislative Day, 1967 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. College Luncheon, 1961 (Box A-416)
    - Conn. Conference of Community and State Safety Officials (missing), 1963 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Council of Senior Citizens, Bridgeport, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Council of Senior Citizens, Lake Compounce, Bristol, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Council on Crime and Delinquency, Conn. General Life Insurance Co., 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Daily Newspaper Association, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Daily Newspaper Association, 1963 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Development Commission Reception, 1963 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Development Conference, 1962 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Editorial Association, 1963 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Editorial Association, 1971 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Educational Television, 1969 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Council for Equal Employment Opportunity, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, Council for, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, Council for, Senate Chamber, Hartford, 1966 May 5 (Box A-417)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, Council for, Gr. Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1966 February 11 (Box A-417)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, Conn. Council for, Hartford, 1965 November 16 (Box A-417)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, Planned Breakfast Meeting, Residence, 1965 June 24 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs, 1962 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Food Stores Association Annual Convention, 1964 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Hotel-Motel Association, Wallingford, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Industrial Building Commission Conference, 1963 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Industrial Development Council, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Industrial Development Tour, 1963 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Industrial Development Council Industrial Tour, 1961 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Institute for the Blind, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Blind, Conn. Institute for the, 1965 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Jaycees, Three Outstanding Young Men Banquet, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Jr. Republic Gymnasium Dedication, Litchfield, 1970 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Library Association, 1967 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Milk Producers" Association Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Milk Producers" Association, 1961 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. National Guard Ceremony in connection with Taking Over for NIKE AJAX Missile Sites, 1961 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Olympics for the Retarded, Storrs (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Pilgrim Fellowship of the Congregational Church, Governor's Office, 1966 August 9 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Public Expenditure Council, Hartford Club, 1966 May 10 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Public Expenditure Council, Hartford Club, Annual Meeting, Hartford, 1963 May 22 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Public Expenditure Council, Hartford Club, 1962 May 22 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Public Expenditure Council, Hartford Club, Hartford, 1961 May 23 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. River National Recreational Area, State Capitol, 1968 September 12 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. River Water Shed Council, East Haddam, 1962 September 29 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Safety Society Annual Conference, Hartford, 1961 June 13 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Safety Society Luncheon, No Release, Prepared Speech, Not Used, 1963 June 11 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Safety Society, Hartford, 1962 June 12 (Box A-417)
    - Gerontology, Conn. Society of, delivered by Mrs. Grasso, Storrs, 1963 October 15 (Box A-417)
    - Gerontology, Conn. Society of, delivered by Lt. Gov. Armentano, Hartford, 1961 October 28 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Employees Annual Convention, Hartford Hilton, 1970 September 26 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Employees Association Convention, Hartford, 1968 October 6 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Employees 26th Annual Convention, Recorded, 1967 October 22 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Employees Association Annual Convention, Hartford, 1966 October 16 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Employees Association, Annual Convention, Hartford, 1965 October 17 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Employees Association, 23rd Annual Convention, Hartford, 1964 October 18 (Box A-417)
    - State Employees Association 22nd Annual Banquet, Hartford, 1963 October 13 (Box A-417)
    - State Employees Association 21st Annual Banquet, Hartford, 1962 October 14 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Employees Association, Hartford, 1961 October 15 (Box A-417)
    - State Employees Freedom Bond Campaign, 1967 September 22 (Box A-417)
    - Council 16 - Annual Convention, 1967 October 26 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Federation of Teachers Convention, New Haven, 1967 October 27 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Grange, Hartford, No Prepared Speech, No Release, 1963 October 17 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. State Grange, Hartford, 1962 October 18 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Transportation Authority, Meeting, Senate Chambers, State Capitol, 1966 July 25 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Transportation Authority Meeting with Interstate Staff Community in New Haven, 1963 December 30 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Valley Hospital, Dedication Ceremonies, 1962 April 30 (Box A-417)
    - Conn. Watershed Management Field Day, West Stafford, 1961 July 12 (Box A-417)
    - Conservation Awards Program, Conn. State League of Sportsmen and Conservation Clubs, Hartford, 1964 November 20 (Box A-417)
    - Governor Dempsey: Conservation Conference of the Natural Resources Council of Conn., Northford, 1966 April 28 (Box A-418)
    - Conservation Field Day, Middlefield - Linus Strickland Farm, 1962 July 28 (Box A-418)
    - Constitution, New, Signing of, Proclamation, December 30, 1965, 1965 December 30 (Box A-418)
    - Constitutional Convention Remarks of Governor, Closing Session, 1965 October 28 (Box A-418)
    - Constitutional Convention Opening Session, Hartford, 1965 July 1 (Box A-418)
    - Corvin Automobile MV Plates Presentation, State Capitol, 1961 October 5 (Box A-418)
    - Correction Dept., Commissioner Ellis C. MacDougall, Swearing in Ceremony, 1968 May 3 (Box A-418)
    - County Adjusters Association, Cheshire, 1962 March 6 (Box A-418)
    - Corrections, Dept. of, Statement by Gov. Dempsey signing of P.A. 152, 1967 May 25 (Box A-418)
    - Council on Aging - 1969, State Capitol, 1969 October 8 (Box A-418)
    - Conference on Crime and Delinquency, Banner Lodge, 1970 September 14 (Box A-418)
    - Cromwell Old Home Day, Cromwell, 1961 June 17 (Box A-418)
    - Cromwell, Assigning NIKE - Hercules Missiles Sites to National Guard, 1964 August 13 (Box A-418)
    - Cuban Prisoners, Remarks by Governor, 1963 July 20 (Box A-418)
    - CYO Communion Breakfast, Sacred Heart Church, Taftville, 1965 February 7 (Box A-418)
    - Governor Dempsey's Nominating Speech for Emilio Daddario, Hartford, 1970 June 27 (Box A-418)
    - Danbury - Dedication of Glen Apartments, Housing for Elderly, 1962 October 4 (Box A-418)
    - Danbury Democratic Dinner, 1966 February 16 (Box A-418)
    - Danbury Rotary Club, Danbury Motor Inn, 1970 October 7 (Box A-418)
    - Danbury Rotary Club - 1969, Danbury Motor Inn, Danbury, 1969 October 1 (Box A-418)
    - Danbury Rotary Club - 1968, Danbury Motor Inn, Danbury, 1968 October 2 (Box A-418)
    - Danbury Rotary Club, Danbury Motor Inn, 1967 October 4 (Box A-418)
    - Rotary Club of Danbury, Luncheon, 1966 October 5 (Box A-418)
    - Rotary Club of Danbury, 1965 October 6 (Box A-418)
    - Danbury State College Commencement, Danbury, 1965 June 13 (Box A-418)
    - Danco Plant, Dedication of, Putnam, September 23, 1966, 1966 September 23 (Box A-418)
    - Danielson Chamber of Commerce, 1962 March 5 (Box A-418)
    - 77th State Conference, Conn. Daughters of the American Revolution, Hartford Hilton, 1970 March 19 (Box A-418)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution Award, State Capitol, 1964 October 8 (Box A-418)
    - Davis - Standard Plant - Dedication Ceremony Pawcatuck, 1964 December 15 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Convention, 1967 December 9 (Box A-418)
    - John M. Bailey Remarks, Democratic Kickoff Dinner, Hartford Hilton, 1970 September 12 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Kickoff Dinner, Hartford Hilton, 1970 September 12 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Campaign Kickoff Dinner, Hartford Hilton, 1968 September 19 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Kickoff Dinner, Hartford, 1964 September 24 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Kickoff Dinner, Hartford, 1962 September 8 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Legislative Campaign Workshop, Hartford, 1968 September 27 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Luncheon, New Britain, 1969 October 24 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic State Convention, Nomination of Abe Ribicoff, Hartford, 1968 June 22 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic State Convention, Remarks of Governor Dempsey, Hartford, 1968 June 21 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic State Convention, Nominating Speech for Senator Dodd, Hartford, 1964 June 6 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic State Convention, Governor's Acceptance Speech, Hartford, 1962 July 14 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Victory Dinner, Hotel Statler, Hartford, 1962 December 18 (Box A-418)
    - Democratic Women's Clubs of Conn., 1967 September 26 (Box A-418)
    - Governor Dempsey's Announcement not to Seek Office, 1970 January 10 (Box A-418)
    - Dedication - John N. Dempsey Regional Center, Putnam, 1969 June 7 (Box A-418)
    - Dental Association, Conn. State, Hartford, 1965 May 27 (Box A-418)
    - Derby - Dedication of James B. Atwater Bridge, 1962 October 25 (Box A-418)
    - Derby - Shelton Board of Trade, Shelton, 1962 April 9 (Box A-418)
    - State Development Commission, Reception, New York, 1968 May 10 (Box A-418)
    - Development Commission 25th Anniversary Dinner, No prepared remarks, Notes only (Box A-418)
    - Development Conference, Conn., Hartford, 1965 November 8 (Box A-418)
    - Development Conference, Statler-Hilton Hotel, Hartford, 1964 November 9 (Box A-418)
    - Development Conference, Conn., Hartford, 1963 October 8 (Box A-418)
    - C. H. Dexter & Sons, Inc., Windsor Locks, 1962 September 26 (Box A-418)
    - Dedication - Dinosaur State Park, Rocky Hill, 1968 October 17 (Box A-418)
    - Dodd Campaign - 1964, Governor's Message following Film on Senator Dodd, Taped, 1964 October 27 (Box A-418)
    - Doocy, Fred J., Lt. Governor's Speech to Conn. Inter- Collegiate Student Legislature, State Capitol, 1966 March 4 (Box A-418)
    - Doocy, Lt. Governor, Fred J., Driver Training, New Legislation - P.A. 765 (Box A-418)
    - Eastern Conn. State College, Annual Leadership Banquet, Willimantic, 1968 May 17 (Box A-418)
    - East Hartford - Dedication of Housing Development for the Elderly, 1963 January 16 (Box A-418)
    - Governor Dempsey: Eastern Star, Order of, Foot Guard Hall, Hartford, 1966 April 22 (Box A-418)
    - Conference on Economic Opportunities for Connecticut's Older Citizens, 1966 February 17 (Box A-418)
    - New England Board of Higher Education, Hartford Hilton, 1969 November 7 (Box A-418)
    - Education, Conference on, State Dept. of Education, Meriden, 1965 July 19 (Box A-419)
    - Education, Annual Meeting, Conn. Association of Boards of Education, Meriden, 1965 October 22 (Box A-419)
    - Education, State Board of, Convocation, Hartford, 1962 October 9 (Box A-419)
    - Boards of Education, Conn. Association, Groton, 1962 September 20 (Box A-419)
    - Conn. Association of Boards of Education, Hartford, 1961 September 15 (Box A-419)
    - Elderly Citizens, Conference on Economic Opportunities, 1966 February 17 (Box A-419)
    - Statement of John Bailey, Election Night, 1968 November 5 (Box A-419)
    - Statements of Governor Dempsey, Election Night, 1968 November 5 (Box A-419)
    - Easter Seals Society, Hotel America, 1969 October 14 (Box A-419)
    - Electric Boat Company, Groton, 1961 October 2 (Box A-419)
    - American Institute of Electrical Engineers, Northeastern District Meeting, 1961 May 17 (Box A-419)
    - Elks Convention, Conn., Windsor, 1965 June 4 (Box A-419)
    - Emanuel Synagogue, Hartford, 120th Anniversary Celebration of Bnai Brith, 1963 December 20 (Box A-419)
    - Emergency Resource Priority Board, Judiciary Committee Room, Capitol, 1967 November 30 (Box A-419)
    - Employment of the Handicapped - Awards Luncheon, 1968 April 16 (Box A-419)
    - Enfield Manor Housing Project for Elderly, Thompsonville, 1964 September 25 (Box A-419)
    - Environmental Policy Committee, State Capitol, Hartford, 1970 January 15 (Box A-419)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Council, State Capitol, 1968 September 17 (Box A-419)
    - Fairfield Democratic Town Committee, 1965 October 30 (Box A-419)
    - Fairfield University Forum, Fairfield, 1968 May 15 (Box A-419)
    - Fairfield Preparatory School, 1967 September 12 (Box A-419)
    - Federal-State Conference, State Capitol, 1967 June 1 (Box A-419)
    - Federal-State Relations Committee, National Governors Conference, Washington, D.C., 1968 February 29 (Box A-419)
    - Farmington Dedication Ceremonies for Yodkins-Morin Memorial Park, 1961 October 7 (Box A-419)
    - Federated Women's Clubs of Hartford, 1963 September 16 (Box A-419)
    - Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs, Hartford Hilton, 1969 May 10 (Box A-419)
    - Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs, Hartford Hilton, September 29, 1965, 1965 September 29 (Box A-419)
    - Democratic Women's Clubs of Conn., State Federation of, Hartford, 1965 April 19 (Box A-419)
    - Conn. State Firemen's Association, Annual Convention, West Haven, 1968 August 16 (Box A-419)
    - Firemen's Association, Conn. State, Annual Convention, New London, Lt. Gov. Doocy, 1966 August 20 (Box A-419)
    - Conn. State Firemen's Association, Plainville, 1964 August 21 (Box A-419)
    - Conn. State Firemen's Association Annual Convention, Naugatuck, 1963 August 23 (Box A-419)
    - Firemen's Association, Conn. State, Annual Convention, Torrington, 1962 August 18 (Box A-419)
    - Conn. State Firemen's Association, Bethel, 1961 August 19 (Box A-419)
    - First Congregational Church, Canterbury, 1966 July 27 (Box A-419)
    - Forest and Park Association, Hall of the House, State Capitol, 1964 April 4 (Box A-419)
    - Founders" Day, Center Church of Hartford, 1962 October 14 (Box A-419)
    - Four-H Club Conference in Storrs, 1963 March 9 (Box A-419)
    - Freedom Fountain Awards at the Hartford Courant, 1966 June 10 (Box A-419)
    - Freedom Club, 25th Anniversary Ball, Windsor, 1964 May 9 (Box A-419)
    - Future Farmers of America, Governor's Remarks on Accepting Degree of Honor State Farmer, 1964 September 17 (Box A-419)
    - Future Farmers of America, 30th Annual Convention, Berlin, 1962 July 16 (Box A-419)
    - Special Message Concerning Tax Issue, 1969 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Closing Speech, 1969 June 4 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Budget Message, 1969 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Closing Speech, 1969 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Opening Session, 1969 January 8 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Closing Message, 1967 June 7 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Budget Message, 1967 February 15 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Inaugural Message, 1967 January 4 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Closing Session, 1965 June 9 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Budget Message, 1965 February 16 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Message, 1965 February 2 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Closing Session, 1963 (Box A-419)
    - General Assembly, Budget Message, 1963 February 14 (Box A-420)
    - General Assembly, Inaugural Message, 1963 (Box A-420)
    - General Assembly, Closing Session, 1961 (Box A-420)
    - General Assembly, Budget Message, 1961 (Box A-420)
    - General Assembly, Message, 1961 January 24 (Box A-420)
    - General Practitioners, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - General Time Corporation, Industrial Controls Division - Plant Dedication, Torrington, 1967 (Box A-420)
    - German-American Day, West Haven, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - Glastonbury Women's Club, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - Golden Milestone Award, Hartford, 1962 (Box A-420)
    - Good Will Industries of Western Connecticut, Fairfield, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Committee on Fitness, Hartford, 1969 (Box A-420)